Thank you very much.
شكراً جزيلاً
Now, I've got a story for you.
و الان سأروي لكم قصة
When I arrived off the plane,
عندما نزلت من الطائرة
after a very long journey from the West of England,
بعد رحلة طويلة من غرب انجلترا
my computer, my beloved laptop,
حاسوبي "المحمول" خاصتي
had gone mad,
تعطل
and had -- oh! -- a bit like that! --
و... اوه شيء من هذا القبيل
and the display on it --
و كان العرض بأكمله عليه
anyway, the whole thing had burst.
على كل حال كل شيء قد اتلف
And I went to the IT guys here
و عندما ذهبت هنا الى فنيّ تكنلوجيا المعلومات
and a gentleman mended my computer,
اصلح شاب محترم حاسوبي
and then he said, "What are you doing here?"
و قال لي "ماذا تفعلين هنا؟"
and I said "I'm playing the cello and I'm doing a bit of singing,"
اجبته "انا اعزف على الة التشيلو, و اغني قليلاً"
and he said, "Oh, I sort of play the cello as well."
ثم قال لي "و انا ايضاً اعزف التشيلو نوعاً ما"
And I said, "Do you really?"
فقلت له "هل تفعل حقاً؟"
Anyway, so you're in for a treat,
على كل حال، أنتي هنا لمعاملة،
because he's fantastic, and his name's Mark.
لانه رائع, و اسمه مارك
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
I am also joined by my partner in crime, Thomas Dolby.
وايضا شاركت زميلي توماس دولبي في مسلسل جريمة
This song is called "Farther than the Sun."
هذه الغنية اسمها "ابعد من الشمس"
(Music)
(موسيقى)
♫ Strung in the wind I called you ♫
♫ناديتك متوترا و انا في وجه الريح♫
♫ but you did not hear ... ♫
♫لكنك لم تسمعني....♫
♫ And you're a plant that needs poor soil ♫
♫وانت محراث بحاجة الى تربة ضعيفة♫
♫ and I have treated you too well ♫
♫و قد عاملتك معاملة حسنة♫
♫ to give up flowers ... ♫
♫لتعطي الزهار♫
♫ Oh, I have been too rich for you ... ♫
و قد كنت طيبا جدا معك♫♫
♫ Farther than the sun from me ♫
♫ابعد عني من الشمس♫
♫ Farther than I'd have you be ♫
♫ابعد مما كنت اعتقد♫
♫ And I go north, I get so cold ♫
♫عندما اتجه شمالا اشعر ببرد شديد♫
♫ My heart is lava under stone ♫
♫لكن قلبي مثل الحمم الدفينة♫
♫ You are not worthy ♫
♫انت لا تستحق♫
♫ With your calculating eyes ♫
♫و بعيونك المخادعة♫
♫ spinning figures ♫
♫تغازل الرشيقات♫
♫ you cannot see me ♫
♫لا يمكنك رؤيتي.♫
♫ You cannot see me ... ♫
♫لا يمكنك رؤيتي...♫
♫ And if I tell myself enough ♫
♫و اذا قررت ان هذه النهاية♫
♫ I'll believe it ♫
♫ستكون كذلك♫
♫ You are not worthy ♫
♫انت لا تستحق♫
♫ The sea, it freezes over ... ♫
ان البحر يتجمد♫
♫ to trap the light ♫
♫ال الافق♫
♫ And I'm in love with being in love ♫
♫و انا احب انني أُحب♫
♫ and you were never quite the one ♫
♫ا نت لم تكن الشخص المناسب♫
♫ In Gerda's eyes ♫
♫من وجهة نظر جيردا♫
♫ Fragments of what you've become ♫
♫انت الان شظايا لما كنت عليه♫
♫ And all the moths that fly at night ♫
♫و ان كل العث الذي يطير ليلاً♫
♫ believe electric light is bright ♫
♫يصدق ان ضوء الكهربائي هو النور♫
♫ You are not worthy ♫
♫انت لا تستحق♫
♫ With your calculating eyes ♫
♫و بعيونك المخادعة♫
♫ Spinning figures ♫
♫تغازل الرشيقات♫
♫ You cannot see me, no ♫
♫لا يمكنك رؤيتي, لا يمكنك♫
♫ And if I tell myself enough ♫
♫و اذا قررت ان هذه النهاية♫
♫ I'll believe it ♫
♫ستكون كذلك♫
♫ You are not worthy ♫
♫انت لا تستحق♫
♫ Farther than the sun from me ♫
♫ابعد عني من الشمس♫
♫ Farther than I'd have you be ♫
♫ابعد مما كنت اعتقد♫
♫ And I go north, I get so cold ♫
♫عندما اتجه شمالا اشعر ببرد شديد♫
♫ My heart is lava under stone ♫
♫لكن قلبي مثل الحمم الدفينة♫
♫ You are not worthy ♫
♫انت لا تستحق♫
♫ With your calculating eyes ♫
♫و بعيونك المخادعة♫
♫ Spinning figures ♫
♫تغازل الرشيقات♫
♫ You cannot see me, no ... ♫
♫لا يمكنك رؤيتي, لا يمكنك♫
♫ And if I tell myself enough, I'll believe it ♫
♫و اذا قررت ان هذه النهاية ستكون كذلك♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Thank you very much.
شكراًجزيلاً لكم